Register of the John Kaye Tabor papers, 1973-1975
Hoover Institution Archives
John Kaye Tabor papers
1973-1975
81074
Hoover Institution Archives
6 manuscript boxes, 1 envelope (2.5 linear feet)
Correspondence, memoranda, speeches, notes, and photographs relating to American economic policy and foreign trade. Mostly photocopies.
Tabor, John Kaye, 1921-1999
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1981.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
U.S. Under Secretary of Commerce, 1973-1975.
Scope and Content of Collection
Correspondence, memoranda, speeches, notes, and photographs relating to American economic policy and foreign trade. Mostly photocopies.
United States. Dept. of Commerce.; United States--Commerce.; United States--Economic policy--1971-1981.; United States--Politics and government--1969-1974.; United States--Politics and government--1974-1977.
- CHRONOLOGICAL FILE, 1973-1975 (Boxes 1-6)
  Scope and Contents note
  Photocopies of correspondence and memoranda, arranged chronologically.
  - 1973
    - July (Box-folder 1: 1)
    - August (Box-folder 1: 2)
    - September (Box-folder 1: 3)
    - October (Box-folder 1: 4)
    - November (Box-folder 2: 1)
    - December (Box-folder 2: 2)
      Includes declassified records returned to file after February 2016 release by Hoover.
  - 1974
    - January (Box-folder 2: 3)
    - February (Box-folder 2: 4)
    - March (Box-folder 2: 5)
    - April (Box-folder 3: 1)
    - May (Box-folder 3: 2)
    - June (Box-folder 3: 3)
    - July (Box-folder 3: 4)
    - August (Box-folder 4: 1)
    - September (Box-folder 4: 2)
    - October (Box-folder 4: 3)
    - November (Box-folder 4: 4)
    - December (Box-folder 5: 1)
  - 1975
    - January (Box-folder 5: 2)
    - February (Box-folder 5: 3)
    - March (Box-folder 5: 4)
    - April (Box-folder 5: 5)
    - May (Box-folder 5: 6)
    - June (Box-folder 6: 1)
    - July (Box-folder 6: 2)
- SPEECH FILE, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 6: 3-4)
  Speeches, notes, press releases, memoranda, and clippings, unarranged.
- APPOINTMENT BOOK, 1974 (Box-folder 6: 5)
- GUEST BOOK, 1975 (Box-folder 6: 6)
- PHOTOGRAPHS, circa 1973-1975 (Photo file)
  - Portraits of John K. Tabor, U.S. Under Secretary of Commerce, 3 prints / 1 envelope (Envelope A)